ASSUMPTIONS

Each car has GPS sensors (always turned on) providing the right coordinates, a board showing the status of the battery level and the charge to users and sensors to check the number of people sitting

Each car can communicate with the central system sending informations through its board (sure?)

The system can always access to the real-time informations of the car, such as its position, the number of people inside it, the battery level and the on-charge status.

Special parking areas are only the ones with power plugs for charging cars

A user can use a car if and only if he has reserved it in advance

A car can be reserved by only a person at a time

A car is unavailable when it has less then 5% of battery level, or it is under maintenance or recharging, or it is already in use or reserved by another user. Otherwise, it is available and shown on maps to users.

The system has access to European Union driving licence databases to verify and approve user registration

The system supports registration only by users having a European driving licence

The system already knows all safe parking areas and identifies them by GPS coordinates

The reservation of a car only ends if the user parks it in a safe parking area, otherwise the user keeps being charged

The car can be driven anywhere in the Italian area. (check position and if user gets out?)

Discounts can be combined so that their total is subtracted to the final charge

Recharge slots can result as available or unavailable and can be reserved by the system for users using money saving method

In case the company receives a fine concerning a bad user behaviour, the user is due to pay it, so the system charges the amount to the user

The system can check the availability of power plugs of all stations at any time


ASSUMPTION?
The user interacts with the system through his mobile phone

DONE
Where the car can be driven? Boundaries
The system accepts only italian driving licence...or european? Can we check.
Each car has sensors to check the number of people sitting
The car has a board showing the status of the battery level
- Car has a gps that always provide the right coordinates
- Gps cannot be turned off (?)
- When a car is available? Battery more than? Position? Not used or reserved by someone else. Broken? Confiscata? Is not being moved by the operator for balancing.
- A parking area cannot have the shape of a donut?
A car has 2 statuses: available - unavailable