	• Car has sensors to understand how many persons there are in the car
	• Car show battery level
	• Car has a gps that always provide the right coordinates
	• Gps cannot be turned off
	• The system can always access real-time to the the position of a car by using GPS, the number of people by sensor, the energy level
	• Each car has a computer board that has access to all the car informations and that communicate with the central system, getting, showing and sending informations.
		○ Who's active? The car or the system?
	• The special parking areas are all and only the ones with a power plug 
	• A user can use a car if and only if he has reserved it in advance
	• A car can be reserved by only a person at time
	• Where the car can be droven? Boundaries
	• When a car is available? Battery more than? Position? Not used or reserved by someone else. Broken? Confiscata? Is not being moved by the operator for balancing.
	• A car have 2 status: available - unavailable
	• The system has the right to access to data of motorizzazione (in req -> check valid, date and level)
	• The system accept only italian driving licence...or european? Can we check.
	• A parking area cannot have the shape of a donut?
The system already knows all safe parking areas and identifies them by gps coordinates